globalguideline.com 2012-06-17

# Global GuideLine Privacy Policy, Tutorials, Interview Questions and Answers

Global GuideLine privacy policy demonstrates our firm commitment to respect the privacy of our respectable visitors. Our aim is to provide safe, informative, reliable and helpful guideline in all aspects of professionals.

## Logging Users Information

For each visitor to our website, our server automatically recognizes only the consumer's IP Address, domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We collect the domain name, IP Address, and e-mail address (where possible) of our respectable visitors to our web page.

| 

| 

The e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, comments, newsletter, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web tutorials, interview questions and answers or articles. These advertising companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our informative material, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our site and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website and Aggregate visitor data is used when to describe user statistics for http://www.globalguideline.com (page views, unique visitors, etc).  We also provide our statistical data on our website just for knowledge you can view our statistical users data here.

## Usage of Cookies at our website.

With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies still at our website.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information, browser etc. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: please visit google.com/adsense. 

## Google Adsense program with us

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our websites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

## Changes of our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. 

If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically or mail us at [ support@globalguideline.com](mailto:support@globalguideline.com) for further questions.

Regards,   
Global GuideLine Team
